647-274-2751 humera.1@hotmail https://ibrahimmanjra.gitlab.io/

# HUMERA MANJRA

# **Front-End Web Developer**

#### **EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE**

## **EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE**

#### **ENGLISH TEACHER**

Larana High School - (2018 – Present)

#### **ENGLISH TEACHER**

Liceria High School - (2014 - 2018)

#### **PROJECTS**

- Poetry Class and Bulletin (2018 – present)
- Drama Club (2016 2018)

### **PROFILE**

Enthusiastic and creative English Teacher with 7+ years of classroom teaching experience. A dedicated teacher who is easily adaptable to different learning styles. Eager to join The Fauget High School to help guarantee student success with skilled instruction.

#### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

Master of Arts in Teaching – English Education Program

2018 -2020

**Fauget University** 

Bachelor of Arts in English Language and Literature

2010 - 2014

**Borcelle University** 

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- Communication skills
- Time management skills
- Modern classroom technology
- Safe and creative classrooms
- Collaboration